https://qtstaffing.com/privacy/

Notice
This organization collects personally identifiable information. Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. uses personally identifiable information to facilitate general business practices, examples of which are sales, marketing, billing, shipping, and accounting uses.
Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. will not sell your personal information to third parties. In the case of the sale of Quik Travel Staffing, Inc., Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. will require the new owner to protect your collected personal information in accordance with this policy. As required, Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. will transfer information to third parties which are either necessary to carry out the transactions pertaining to the customer or are necessary to facilitate general business practices such as to outside accounting, billing or delivery companies.
Security
Realizing the importance of secure data, Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. takes reasonable precautions to protect personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Security questions regarding Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. should be directed to:
Quik Travel Staffing, Inc.
175 East Olive Ave., Suite 405
Burbank, California 91502
Data Integrity
Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. processes personal information only in a way that is compatible with the purposes for which it was collected and authorized by the individual. To the extent necessary for those purposes, Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. takes reasonable steps to ensure that data is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current. Please send your updated information to CustomerService@QTStaffing.com.
Access
Subject to limitations, Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. customers have the right to access to their own non-public personal information in order to correct, amend, or delete the information where it is inaccurate. In order to supply Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. with sufficient information to allow it to confirm the identity of the person making the request, Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. requires the requesting party to fill out an access form available from the address below. Return the form along with a US $15.00 to the same address from which the form was obtained.
To receive an access request form send a self addressed stamped envelope to:
Quik Travel Staffing, Inc.
175 East Olive Ave., Suite 405
Burbank, California 91502
Log Files
IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
Links
This web site may contains links to other sites. Please be aware that this site is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Quik Travel Staffing, Inc.
Enforcement
If a customer has a compliant regarding Quik Travel Staffing, Inc.’s use of their personal information, please contact Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. directly at 1 (800) 554-2230, or by writing:
Quik Travel Staffing, Inc.
175 East Olive Ave., Suite 405
Burbank, California 91502
Or by emailing CustomerService@QTStaffing.com
Notification of Changes
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to update or revise this privacy statement. Please check this statement periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any changes to the privacy statement constitutes acceptance of those changes. If you have any questions regarding any aspect of Quik Travel Staffing, Inc.’s privacy policy please email your inquiries to CustomerService@QTStaffing.com.
Terms and Conditions
By using this site you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions:
DISCLAIMER
Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. makes no warranties or representations about the accuracy or completeness of this Site’s content.
COPYRIGHTS AND TRADEMARKS
The entire content included in this Site, including but not limited to text, design, graphics, interfaces, or code and the selection and arrangements thereof is copyrighted as a collective work under the United States and other copyright laws, and is the property of Quik Travel Staffing, Inc.. Copyright 2000-2009. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. All trademarks, service marks, and trade names are trademarks or registered trademarks of and are proprietary to Quik Travel Staffing, Inc., or other respective owners that have granted Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. the right and license to use such Marks.
THIS SITE AND THE MATERIALS, INFORMATION, SERVICES, AND PRODUCTS IN THIS SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, TEXT, GRAPHICS, AND LINKS, ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, QUIK TRAVEL STAFFING, INC. DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, FREEDOM FROM COMPUTER VIRUS, AND WARRANTIES ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEALING OR COURSE OF PERFORMANCE. QUIK TRAVEL STAFFING, INC. DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS CONTAINED IN THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THIS SITE, THE SERVER THAT MAKES THE SITE AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. QUIK TRAVEL STAFFING, INC. DOES NOT MAKE ANY WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OF PRODUCTS OR OF THE MATERIALS IN THIS SITE IN TERMS OF THEIR COMPLETENESS, CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, ADEQUACY, USEFULNESS, TIMELINESS, RELIABILITY OR OTHERWISE. THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
IN NO EVENT SHALL QUIK TRAVEL STAFFING, INC. BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL, DAMAGES, OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, EVEN IF QUIK TRAVEL STAFFING, INC. HAS BEEN PREVIOUSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION UNDER CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, OR ANY OTHER THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE, INABILITY TO USE, OR PERFORMANCE OF THE INFORMATION, SERVICES, PRODUCTS, AND MATERIALS AVAILABLE FROM THIS SITE. THESE LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY NOT WITHSTANDING ANY FAILURE OF ESSENTIAL PURPOSE OF ANY LIMITED REMEDY. BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY LASTS, OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
INDEMNIFICATION
Site user hereby agrees to indemnify, defend and hold harmless this web site and its owners from and against all losses, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees resulting from the use of this web site. Under no circumstances, including negligence, shall this web site, its officers and employees, agents, subcontractors, or anyone else involved in creating, producing or distributing its services, be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages that result from the use of or inability to use this web site even if this web site has been advised of the possibility of such damages; or that results from mistakes, omissions, interruptions, deletion or loss of files or data, errors, defects, delays in operation, or of performance, whether or not limited to acts of God, communication failure, theft, destruction or unauthorized access to this web site’s records, programs or services.
APPLICABLE LAWS
Your use of this Site shall be governed in all respects by the laws of the State of California, U.S.A., without regard to choice of law provisions, and not by the 1980 U.N. Convention on contracts for the international sale of goods. You agree that jurisdiction over and venue in any legal proceeding directly or indirectly arising out of or relating to this Site shall be in the state or federal courts located in Los Angeles County, California. Any cause of action or claim you may have with respect to the Site must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises. Quik Travel Staffing, Inc.’s failure to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of these terms and conditions shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. Neither the course of conduct between the parties nor trade practice shall act to modify any of these terms and conditions. Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. may assign its rights and duties under this Agreement to any party at any time without notice to you.
Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. makes no representation that materials in the Site are appropriate or available for use in other locations, and access to them from territories where their content is illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access this Site from locations outside California do so at their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. You may not use or export the materials in violation of U.S. export laws and regulations. Any claim relating to the materials shall be governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of California.
ARBITRATION
By using this Site, you agree that Quik Travel Staffing, Inc., at its sole discretion, may require you to submit any disputes arising from the use of this Site, or these Terms and Conditions concerning or, including disputes arising from or concerning their interpretation, violation, nullity, invalidity, non-performance or termination, as well as disputes about filling gaps in this contract or its adaptation to newly arisen circumstances, to final and binding arbitration under the International Rules of Arbitration of the American Arbitration Association, by one or more arbitrators appointed in accordance with the said Rules. Notwithstanding these rules, however, such proceeding shall be governed by the laws of the state as set forth in the previous section. Any award in an arbitration initiated under this clause shall be limited to monetary damages and shall include no injunction or direction to any party other than the direction to pay a monetary amount. Further, the arbitrator(s) shall have no authority to award punitive, consequential or other damages not measured by the prevailing party’s actual damages in any arbitration initiated under this section, except as may be required by statute.
TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS
In the event Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. product or service is listed at an incorrect price due to typographical error or error in pricing information received from our suppliers, Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. shall have the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed for product or service listed at the incorrect price. Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. shall have the right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged.
SEVERANCE
If any provision of this Agreement is found to be invalid by any court having jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of this Agreement, which shall remain in full force and effect.
ENTIRE AGREEMENT
Except as provided herein, these terms and conditions are the entire agreement between us and supersede any prior understanding or agreements (written or oral).
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
Quik Travel Staffing, Inc. reserves the right, at our discretion, to update or revise these Terms and Conditions of use. Please check this statement periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any changes to the Terms and Conditions constitutes acceptance of those changes. If you have any questions regarding any aspect of Quik Travel Staffing, Inc.’s Terms and Conditions please email your inquiries to CustomerService@QTStaffing.com.
contact  |  privacy  |  legal  |  employee handbook  |  CEUs
All content © Quik Travel Staffing
